cashiecommerce.com 2016-10-22

# Cashie Commerce Privacy Policy

**Announcement:** The Cashie Commerce service will be shutting down permanently on September 30, 2016.  
You will no longer be charged for this service. Please take the necessary actions to move to an alternative service.

This site (the "Site") is owned by Cashie Commerce, Inc., a Delaware corporation ("us," "we," or "Company"). We created this Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") to explain how we use the information we collect on the Site. This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Site, and not to any other websites that you may be able to access from the Site, each of which may have data collection, storage, and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy.

### Information We Collect

We automatically track and collect the following categories of information when you visit our Site: 1) IP addresses; 2) domain servers; 3) types of computers accessing the Site; and 4) types of web browsers used to access the Site (collectively "Traffic Data"). Traffic Data is anonymous information that does not personally identify you but is helpful for marketing purposes or for improving your experience on the Site. We also use "cookies" to customize content specific to your interests and to ensure that you do not see the same advertisement repeatedly.

Cashie™ is an application service that we make available through the site for you to use in connection with a website that you develop. In order for us to be able to contact you about your use of Cashie, we require you to provide us with certain information that personally identifies you ("Personal Information"). Personal Information includes the following categories of information: 1) Contact Data (such as your name, company name, contact information, and PayPal email address); 2) Financial Data (such as the credit/debit account information for the account you want to establish for billing purposes); and Transaction Data (such as a website's inventory, the content of a consumer's online shopping cart, as well as consumer purchase and payment information). If you communicate with us by e-mail, post messages to any of our chat groups, bulletin boards, or forums, or otherwise complete online forms, surveys, or contest entries, any information provided in such communication may be collected as Personal Information.

### Our Use of Collected Information

We use Personal Information to enable the development and use of e-commerce functionality; to communicate with you about Cashie, your use of Cashie, and other related products and services in which we think you may be interested; and to customize and tailor your experience on our Site. 

We do not sell, license, transfer, and/or share the billing information we collect from you, other than for billing purposes. We use an unaffiliated, credit card processing company to process your payments. We transfer your payment information—and you authorize us to do so—to this company solely for this purpose. The company does not retain, share, store, or use your personally identifiable information for any other purposes. We use the Transaction Data we collect to enable a consumer's purchase to be processed. We do this by passing the Transaction Data to PayPal. We also collect and analyze non-personally identifiable Transaction Data and the associated IP address to help us improve Cashie.

You may choose not to provide us with any Personal Information. In such an event, you will not be able to access and use our Site or develop a site that uses Cashie. If you do not wish to receive information and promotional material from us or, you may "opt-out" by not providing the information when we ask you for Personal Information.

### Confidentiality and Security of Personal Information

We may also (and you authorize us to) disclose your personal information to: a) comply with a court order or other legal process or inquiry; b) protect our rights or property; or c) enforce our Terms of Use. Your Personal Information is stored on secure servers that are not accessible by third parties. We provide you with the capability to transmit your Personal Information via secured and encrypted channels if you use a similarly equipped web browser.

We maintain a procedure in order to help you confirm that your Personal Information remains correct and up-to-date. At any time, you may review your personal profile by accessing your account settings at http://www.cashiecommerce.com/account. You may: a) review and update your Personal Information that we have already collected and/or b) choose whether or not you wish for us to sell, license, transfer, and/or share your Personal Information with third parties.

The Site contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We also make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and news groups available to you. Please understand that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. We have no control over its use and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your Personal Information.

This Site is directed at teenagers and adults and not to children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, nor do we knowingly distribute such information. We do not knowingly allow children under the age of 13 to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information through our website. Similarly, because we do not collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, we do not condition the participation of a child under 13 in activities on providing personally identifiable information. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personally identifiable information from someone under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records. If we change our practices in the future, we will obtain prior, verifiable parental consent before collecting any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13.

We have implemented a number of security measures to help protect against the loss, misuse or modification of information we've collected from you. Your personal information is transmitted to and stored on servers that we have taken steps to protect from unauthorized access or intrusion. We do not ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. You acknowledge and assume this risk.

We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update, or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on the Site and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site.

This site is owned and operated by Cashie Commerce, Inc. 3830 Valley Ctr Dr #705-141, San Diego, CA 92130.

Last Revised: January 1, 2012
